<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="overview_category">Toronto</string>
    <string name="know_toronto">T.O.</string>
    <string name="architecture_category">Architecture</string>
    <string name="restaurant_category">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="shopping_category">Shopping</string>
    <string name="music_and_nightlife_category">Music and Nightlife</string>

    <string name="address_title">Address</string>
    <string name="contact_title">Contact</string>
    <string name="take_me_text">take me</string>
    <string name="bonjour_text">bonjour!</string>

    <string name="toronto_eton_center">Start your day off at one of the city’s most iconic
        shopping hubs – Toronto Eaton Centre. Conveniently located downtown on Yonge Street between
        Queen and Dundas, this stylish mall is a Toronto landmark. Snap a photo in front of the
        famous Canada Geese sculpture flying overhead before strolling beneath the spectacular glass
        galleria and exploring the more than 230 retailers, restaurants and services.
    \n\nAllocate at least an hour and a half to spend here. Start off at Hudson’s Bay on Queen Street
        (the company’s flagship location) where you can find high-end designer items in The Room,
        a Saks Fifth Avenue (!) as well as mid-priced merchandise throughout the store. Then explore
        some of the mall’s many other highlights, including J. Crew, a flagship HnM and the
        Apple Store. Once you’ve worked up an appetite, head to the sprawling food court where
        numerous culinary options await.</string>

    <string name="yorkville_village">Make your way to Toronto’s most upscale shopping district –
        Bloor-Yorkville, also known as the “Mink Mile.” With price tags ranging into the thousands
        of dollars, this is not shopping for the faint of heart (or the budget-constrained).
    \n\nIn Yorkville Village, Bloor-Yorkville’s high-end shopping centre, sought-after fashion brands
        are ripe for the picking at specialty boutiques like Marina Rinaldi, NANNI and Via Cavour. 
        You can also venture outside of the mall and explore the many designer stores lining Bloor 
        Street – Tiffany n Co., Prada, Chanel and Louis Vuitton, to name a few. Window shopping is 
        encouraged!</string>

    <string name="yorkdale_shopping_center">Take a short drive (or subway ride) northwest to
        Yorkdale Shopping Centre. This mall packs an impressive range of merchandise – everything
        from books to toys to fashion to kitchenware – into its 250-plus stores. In addition to an
        array of fashion and accessory stores, Yorkdale has recently opened its doors to unique
        retailers like The LEGO Store and Zara Home.
    \n\nExplore at your leisure before grabbing a snack at one of the mall’s sit-down restaurants
        (Moxie’s or Milestone’s are always popular choices).
        Then pack your bags back into the car to continue your shopping extravaganza.</string>

    <string name="vaughn_mills">A bit north of Toronto in the city of Vaughan (easily accessible via
        Highway 400) lies Vaughan Mills shopping centre. Anchored by fifteen retailers including Saks
        OFF 5th, The Children’s Place and Victoria’s Secret, this outlet retail complex is a
        shopper’s dream.
    \n\nOutdoorsy types should be sure to head to the massive Bass Pro Shops Outdoor World, replete
        with hunting, fishing and camping gear. And if you’re toting tots, treat them with a trip to
        the 40,000 square foot LEGOLAND Discovery Centre, complete with rides, 4D cinema, Master
        Model Builder workshops and impressive LEGO reconstructions of Toronto’s most iconic
        attractions.</string>

    <string name="square_one">Make your way southwest to Mississauga, where more retail delights
        await. Square One is the largest mall in Ontario, boasting over 360 stores and services in
        more than 1.6 million square feet of space. You’ll feel like Dorothy in the Emerald City as
        you explore its many shops.
    \n\nHigh-end fashion is the name of the game at boutiques like Ann Taylor, M for Mendocino and
        Stars Mens. And with Ben Sherman and Simons opening in March 2016, the fashion game gets
        kicked up an extra notch. And of course there are plenty of specialty stores for
        accessories, footwear, electronics and more.</string>

    <string name="sherway_garden">A short hop, skip and jump away from Square One lies Sherway
        Gardens. Easy to spot due to its distinctive tented roof, Sherway Gardens has a geometric
        layout that makes it feel like you’re strolling the streets of a well-maintained shopping
        district.
        \n\nCheck out Saks Fifth Avenue or Rinascimento women’s wear. For high-end men’s apparel,
        head to Harry Rosen. If you prefer a one-stop shopping experience, it’s hard to beat the
        selection of quality merchandise at Holt Renfrew. </string>

    <string name="dixie_outlet_malls">Wind down your evening at Dixie Outlet Mall, where you can
        find designer clothing for a fraction of the regular price. Canada’s largest enclosed
        outlet mall boasts several brand name outlets – such as Guess, Mexx, Tommy Hilfiger, and
        Levis – in addition to regular non-outlet stores like Ricki’s and Fairweather.
    \nThe only thing better than getting that perfect pair of designer jeans is getting them 30%-70%
        off regular retail price. You’ll be surprised at what treasures you can find with a bit of
        bargain-hunting at Dixie Outlet Mall!</string>

    <string name="toronto_premium_outlet">Can’t find exactly what you’re looking for at Dixie
        Outlet Mall? Toronto Premium Outlets may have what you crave. Although a bit farther out
        from the city core, the impressive collection of high-end brands for outlet prices is sure
        to appeal to bargain-hunters of all stripes.
        \n\nDesigner fashions and sportswear outlets include everything from Adidas to Hugo Boss
        to Ted Baker London to Zumiez. Whichever time of year you go, you’re guaranteed to find
        impressive savings at Toronto Premium Outlets.</string>

    <string name="terroni">There’s always something delicious cooking at Terroni.
        With its rustic décor, comfortable seating and laid-back atmosphere, this Southern 
        Italian-inspired restaurant is a great place for a family meal. You’ll love the selection 
        of fresh pastas and extensive wine list, while your kids will love the 28 pizza options and
        dessert menu.</string>

    <string name="barbqe_smokehouse">Barque Smokehouse offers delicious, feel-good barbecue fare 
        that will have everyone licking their fingers (and plates!). Its Kid’s Menu includes a 
        drink, meat selection, side dish and cookie or gelato for $10.00. Also, every Sunday is 
        family night, which means huge and affordable platters for sharing…</string>

    <string name="il_fornello">Danforth Avenue is known mainly for its numerous Greek restaurants,
        but Il Fornello serves up Italian fare that rivals the best of them. From calamari, to
        chicken parmigiana, to seafood linguini, there’s plenty here to appeal to mature palates.
        Smaller mouths will love the spaghetti n meatballs and pepperoni pizza.</string>

    <string name="uncle_bettys">Family owned and operated, Uncle Betty’s Diner specializes in 
        gourmet comfort food that is enticing to kids and kids-at-heart alike. Options for all 
        ages include hotdogs and sloppy joes, while their dedicated 13-and-under menu features 
        other kid-approved favourites like mac ‘n cheese and chicken fingers. The ice cream bar 
        provides a sweet ending to a tasty meal.</string>

    <string name="the_ace">The children’s menu at The Ace includes more than your standard fare.
        Yes, there’s grilled cheese and spaghetti, but there’s also more sophisticated dishes
        like broccoli with aged cheddar sauce. Grown-ups have options ranging from arugula salad
        to Ace’s famous country-fried chicken, any of which can be paired with a cocktail or glass
        of wine from the extensive drink menu.</string>

    <string name="magic_oven">Known for its healthy pizzas made with fresh, local and organic 
        ingredients and Magic Oven has multiple locations around the city. You’ll find plenty of 
        families at the Danforth location on Mondays between 5 p.m. and 9 p.m., when kids eat free.
        The kids’ menu comes with a quiz and puzzles to keep tots occupied while they wait for their
        food to arrive. Nutritious and delicious!</string>

    <string name="mandarin">With several locations in the Greater Toronto Area, Mandarin has long 
        been a favourite destination for families. Its all-you-can-eat Chinese-Canadian buffet 
        provides options for all tastes. If your kids aren’t crazy about wonton soup and maki rolls,
        they can always head for the oven-baked pizzas and barbecued chicken instead.</string>

    <string name="the_old_spaghetti_factory">Just steps away from St. Lawrence Market, located in a 
        historical blacksmith shop and decked out in turn-of-the-century décor, The Old Spaghetti 
        Factory is a kid magnet. A bustling place where it’s okay to be noisy, you can grab a cozy
        booth bathed in the vintage warm glow of the restaurant’s many stained-glass lamps. 
        For added fun, try one of more unique tables, in a streetcar, on a 100-year old carousel 
        or even on a king-sized bed!</string>

    <string name="pan_on_danforth">Opa! A star on the Danforth’s constellation of Greek restaurants,
        Pan on the Danforth has been providing loyal customers with delicious Hellenic fare,
        entertainment (including live music and belly dancers), and dazzling table-side service
        for 10 years. Truly a Toronto institution, Pan will have everyone in your party mesmerized
        and totally sated.</string>

    <string name="lisbon_by_night">A popular spot for family get-togethers and celebrations, this authentic
        Portuguese gem cooks up a delicious “rodizio” fish exactly like how they used to in the old
        country. Kids who haven’t developed a taste for seafood yet can fill up on chicken fingers
        or penne with tomato sauce. Live music on the weekends provides entertainment for the whole
        family.</string>

    <string name="lost_and_found">oused in the lower level of a hundred year-old building in the
        heart of King West, Lost and Found presents a unique space for discovery. The old brick
        walls contrasted with the swanky leather couches give this nightspot an air of classic
        meets modern. It’s a popular hangout on Monday nights when most other clubs are closed.
        Come to lose yourself in the music – and find new friendships, relationships, and
        experiences.</string>

    <string name="uniun">Partying at Uniun is more than just a night out; it’s an experience.
        Conceived by nightlife visionary Charles Khabouth as “the first of its kind,” Uniun boasts
        LED-light installations, a state-of-the-art sound system, and a unique industrial décor.
        Lush VIP banquet seating is contrasted by cement walls, factory beams, and bronzed metal
        arches awash in the glow of bright coloured lights. Uniun is a mishmash of old and new that
        all comes together to create a multisensory experience like no other.</string>

    <string name="coda">If you want another spot out of the club district where you can still enjoy
        a butt-kicking sound system, CODA in the Annex neighbourhood is worth your time. A mix of
        dressed up clubbers and band T-shirt wearing partiers populates the dance floor and the
        surrounding seating area. You can even get a bite to eat there if you’ve burned up all your
        calories on the floor.</string>

    <string name="cube">With its retro ‘70s design, high ceilings, and extensive selection of
        bottles and beverages, Cube styles itself as “the next dimension of entertainment and style.
        ” A large dancefloor, private booths, and comfortable beige-leather lounge offer multiple
        options for an evening of fun. Upstairs, the rooftop patio provides stunning views of the
        Toronto skyline and is always a hot spot during the Toronto International Film Festival for
        celeb-filled parties.</string>

    <string name="nest">Found on College Street, away from the club district, every weekend Nest
        can be counted on to be blasting the best club bangers. From well-known international DJs to
        local up-and-coming talent, and a massive DYNACORD sound system, enjoy big sound and cold
        drinks where the dancefloor is always happening.</string>

    <string name="maison_mercer">A hot crowd of party-goers, stylish interior and ultramodern sound
        system – what more can you ask for from a nightclub? Centrally located in the heart of the
        Entertainment District, this 12,000 square foot multi-level venue boasts a rooftop patio,
        elevated seating areas, performance stage, dance floor, catering kitchen, LED lighting and
        video screens and advanced sound system. Whether for a private event, live performance or
        weekend dance party, Maison is a place to see and be seen.</string>

    <string name="efs_toronto">Catering to young professionals and businesspeople in the King West
        area, EFS has a rooftop patio that is the envy of many of Toronto’s other nightclubs.
        Inspired by a piece of art, EFS stands for “Everything’s for Sale.” Private cabanas
        (equipped with hookahs) line the patio, making it an ideal spot to chill out with friends.
        Try one of EFS’s signature cocktails, developed by a real mixologist.</string>

    <string name="the_rex">At The Rex you can catch live jazz seven days a
        week. Here, local luminaries like Rich Brown and Don Thompson share the stage with
        international acts such as Snarky Puppy. With its full lineup of fine musicians, casual
        atmosphere and affordable drink menu, The Rex has been the go-to spot for jazz on Queen
        West for over 40 years.</string>

    <string name="reservoir_loundge">In the heart of downtown Toronto, The Reservoir Lounge
        is one of the hippest lounges in the city. Exposed brick walls and dim lighting give
        this basement venue a relaxed martini-swirling vibe, but don’t be fooled – once the
        band takes the stage the dance floor abounds with energy. It was at The Reservoir Lounge
        that a young unknown named Michael Bublé first made a name for himself.</string>

    <string name="cn_tower">Toronto’s most famous landmark is more than just an engineering wonder
        – it’s also an award-winning dining and entertainment destination. Standing at 553 metres
        (1,815 feet) the CN Tower held the distinction of being the tallest free-standing structure
        in the world until the completion of Burj Khalifa in 2010. Today it is one of Toronto’s
        most popular attractions for tourists and locals alike and on June 26, 2016 it turned 40!</string>

    <string name="new_city_hall">While the buildings base is rectangular,
        its two towers are curved in cross-section and rise to differing heights.
        The east tower is 27 storeys (99.5 metres (326 ft)) tall and the west tower is 20 storeys
        (79.4 metres (260 ft)). Between the towers is the saucer-like council chamber, and the
        overall arrangement is somewhat like two hands cradling the chamber</string>

    <string name="old_city_hall">Toronto\'s Old City Hall was one of the largest buildings in Toronto
        and the largest civic building in North America upon completion in 1899.
        It was the burgeoning city\'s third city hall. It housed Toronto\'s municipal government
        and courts for York County and Toronto, taking over from the Adelaide Street Court House.
        York County offices were also located in Old City Hall from 1900 to 1953.
        With the establishment of Metropolitan Toronto, the county seat moved to
        Newmarket, Ontario (and to the Old Newmarket Town Hall and Courthouse).</string>

    <string name="art_gallary_of_ontario">With a collection of more than 90,000 works of art,
        the Art Gallery of Ontario (AGO) is among the largest and most distinguished art museums
        in North America. An international landmark, the AGO is also one of Canada’s most innovative
        cultural destinations. Highlights of the Gallery’s world-class collection include iconic
        \n\nCanadian and Inuit works, along with European and contemporary art – all on view in a
        spectacular building transformed by renowned Toronto-born architect Frank Gehry. After
        spending time with the AGO’s vast collection, be sure to enjoy a meal or glass of wine
        at the Gallery’s award-winning restaurant FRANK. Visit shopAGO for a unique collection
        of artful gifts, one-of-a-kind jewelry, and beautiful art books.</string>

    <string name="royal_ontario_museum">Opened in 1914, the Royal Ontario Museum (ROM)
        showcases art, culture, and nature from around the globe and across the ages.
        One of North America\'s most renowned cultural institutions, Canada\'s largest museum is
        home to a world-class collection of more than six million objects and specimens, featured
        in 40 gallery and exhibition spaces. As the country\’s preeminent field research institute
        and an international leader in new and original findings in biodiversity, palaeontology,
        earth sciences, the visual arts, material culture and archaeology, the ROM plays a vital
        role in advancing our global understanding of the artistic, cultural and natural world.
        \n\nThe Renaissance ROM expansion project (2007) merged the iconic architectural heritage of
        the original building with the Studio Daniel Libeskind-designed Michael Lee-Chin Crystal.
        A distinctive new symbol of Toronto for the 21st century, the Crystal marked the beginning
        of a new era for the ROM as the country\'s premier cultural and social destination.</string>


    <string name="commerce_court_north">The Commerce Court complex opened its doors in the early
        1970’s, but with the inclusion of Commerce Court North into the four-acre complex,
        its history reaches back to 1931. It’s hard to imagine today, but the 34-storey North
        Tower was the tallest building in the British Empire until 1962 and home to Canada’s
        business elite for a generation. It was designed by Pearson and Darling Architects of
        Toronto, with the help of U.S. design firm York and Sawyer.
        \n\nWith its stunning vaulted
        gold-coffered ceiling and classic Art-Deco style, the North Tower was a showplace in its
        time, and today remains a treasured heritage building in Toronto’s financial core and a
        major component of Commerce Court.</string>

    <string name="roy_thompson_hall">Roy Thomson Hall is a concert hall in Toronto, Ontario, Canada.
        Located downtown in the city\'s entertainment district, it is home to the Toronto Symphony
        Orchestra and Toronto Mendelssohn Choir. Opened in 1982, its circular architectural design
        exhibits a sloping and curvilinear glass exterior. It was designed by Canadian architects
        Arthur Erickson and Mathers and Haldenby. The hall seats 2,630 guests and features a pipe
        organ built by Canadian organ builders Gabriel Kney of London, Ontario.</string>

    <string name="union_station">Union Station is a major railway station and intermodal
        transportation hub in Toronto, Ontario, Canada. It is located on Front Street West,
        on the south side of the block bounded by Bay Street and York Street in downtown Toronto.
        The station building is owned by the City of Toronto, while the train shed and trackage
        is owned by the commuter rail operator GO Transit. Union Station has been designated a
        National Historic Site of Canada since 1975, and a Heritage Railway Station since 1989.</string>

    <string name="the_royal_york">The Fairmont Royal York, formerly the Royal York, is a large
        historic hotel in downtown Toronto, Ontario, Canada, at 100 Front Street West.
        Opened on June 11, 1929, the Royal York was designed by Ross and Macdonald
        (with Sproatt and Rolph) and built by the Canadian Pacific Railway across the street from
        Toronto Union Station. With 28 floors, the Château-style building was the tallest building
        in Toronto at that time, and the tallest building in the British Empire until the
        construction of Canadian Bank of Commerce tower on King Street the following year.</string>

    <string name="overview_text">Toronto is Canada\'s largest city, the fourth largest in North America,
        and home to a diverse population of about 2.8 million people. It\'s a global centre for
        business, finance, arts and culture and is consistently ranked
        one of the world\'s most livable cities. Toronto, the capital of the province of Ontario,
        is a major Canadian city along Lake Ontario’s northwestern shore.
        \n\nIt\'s a dynamic metropolis with a core of soaring skyscrapers, all dwarfed by the iconic,
        free-standing CN Tower. Toronto also has many green spaces,
        from the orderly oval of Queen’s Park to 400-acre High Park and its trails, sports facilities and zoo.</string>

    <!-- Architecture name and addresses -->
    <string name="cn_tower_title">CN Tower</string>
    <string name="cn_tower_address">301 Front St W</string>
    <string name="new_city_hall_title">New City Hall</string>
    <string name="new_city_hall_address">100 Queen St W</string>
    <string name="old_city_hall_title">Old City Hall</string>
    <string name="old_city_hall_address">60 Queen St W</string>
    <string name="art_gallery_title">Art Gallery of Ontario</string>
    <string name="art_gallery_address">317 Dundas St W</string>
    <string name="royal_ontario_museum_title">Royal Ontario Museum</string>
    <string name="royal_ontario_museum_address">100 Queens Park</string>
    <string name="commerce_court_north_title">Commerce Court North</string>
    <string name="commerce_court_north_address">199 Bay St, Ground Floor</string>
    <string name="roy_thompson_hall_title">Roy Thompson Hall</string>
    <string name="roy_thompson_hall_address">60 Simcoe St</string>
    <string name="union_station_title">Union Station</string>
    <string name="union_station_address">Union Station</string>
    <string name="royal_york_title">The Royal York</string>
    <string name="royal_york_address">100 Front St W</string>

    <!-- Night clubs name and addresses -->
    <string name="lost_and_found_title">Lost and Found</string>
    <string name="lost_and_found_Address">577 King Street West</string>
    <string name="cube_title">Cube</string>
    <string name="cube_address">314 Queen Street West</string>
    <string name="nest_title">Nest</string>
    <string name="nest_address">423 College Street</string>
    <string name="coda_title">Coda</string>
    <string name="coda_address">794 Bathurst Street</string>
    <string name="union_title">Union</string>
    <string name="union_address">473 Adelaide Street West</string>
    <string name="maison_mercer_title">Maison Mercer</string>
    <string name="maison_mercer_address">15 Mercer Street</string>
    <string name="efs_toronto_title">EFS Toronto</string>
    <string name="efs_toronto_address">647 King Street West</string>
    <string name="the_rex_title">The Rex</string>
    <string name="the_rex_address">149 Queen Street West</string>
    <string name="the_reservoir_lounge_title">The Reservoir Lounge</string>
    <string name="the_reservoir_lounge_address">52 Wellington Street</string>

    <!-- Restaurant names and addresses -->
    <string name="terroni_title">Terroni</string>
    <string name="terroni_address">"720 Queen Street West"</string>
    <string name="smokehouse_title">Barbque Smokehouse</string>
    <string name="smokehouse_address">1299 Roncesvalles Avenue</string>
    <string name="il_fornello_title">Il Fornello</string>
    <string name="il_fornello_address">576 Danforth Avenue</string>
    <string name="uncle_betty_title">Uncle Betty\'s Dinner</string>
    <string name="uncle_betty_address">2590 Yonge Street</string>
    <string name="the_ace_title">The Ace</string>
    <string name="the_ace_address">231a Roncesvalles Avenue</string>
    <string name="magic_oven_title">Magic Oven</string>
    <string name="magic_oven_address">798 Danforth Avenue</string>
    <string name="mandarin_title">Mandarin</string>
    <string name="mandarin_address">2200 Yonge Street</string>
    <string name="spaghetti_factory_title">The Old Spaghetti Factory</string>
    <string name="spaghetti_factory_address">54 The Esplanade</string>
    <string name="pan_title">PAN on The Danforth</string>
    <string name="pan_address">516 Danforth Avenue</string>
    <string name="libson_title">Libson by Night</string>
    <string name="libson_address">802 Dundas Street West</string>

    <!-- Shopping malls names and addresses -->
    <string name="eaton_center_title">Toronto Eaton Center</string>
    <string name="eaton_center_address">220 Yonge St</string>
    <string name="yorkville_vilage_title">Yorkville Village</string>
    <string name="yorkville_village_address">55 Avenue Rd</string>
    <string name="yorkdale_shopping_title">Yorkdale Shopping Center</string>
    <string name="yorkdale_shopping_address">3401 Dufferin Street, North York</string>
    <string name="vaughn_mills_title">Vaughn Mills</string>
    <string name="vaughn_mills_address">1 Bass Pro Mills Dr, Concord</string>
    <string name="square_one_title">Square One</string>
    <string name="square_one_address">100 City Centre Dr, Mississauga</string>
    <string name="sherway_garderns_title">Sherway Gardens</string>
    <string name="sherway_gardens_address">25 The West Mall, Etobicoke</string>
    <string name="dixie_mall_title">Dixie Outlet Malls</string>
    <string name="dixie_mall_address">1250 S Service Rd, Mississauga</string>
    <string name="toronto_outlets_title">Toronto Premium Outlets</string>
    <string name="toronto_outlets_address">13850 Steeles Avenue W, Halton Hills</string>
</resources>
